Black Sparrow Press Collection, 1966-1994 (bulk 1973-1993)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: General Correspondence, 1971-1982
  - Gifford, Barry, 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 281, Folder 19)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1980 (Box 281, Folder 20)
  - Gnomen Press, 1975, 1980-1981 (Box 281, Folder 21)
  - Godine, David R., Publisher, Inc., 1981 (Box 281, Folder 22)
  - Goodman, Percival, 1981 (Box 281, Folder 23)
  - Gotham Book Mart, 1980-1981 (Box 281, Folder 25)
  - Goyen, William, 1978, 1982 (Box 281, Folder 26)
  - Graphic and Allied Systems, 1977-1979 (Box 281, Folder 27)
  - Gray, Joan, 1980, 1982 (Box 281, Folder 28)
  - Grey Fox Press, 1979 (Box 281, Folder 29)
  - Grossinger, Richard, 1975-1981 (Box 281, Folder 30)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1978-1980 (Box 281, Folder 31)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1978-1980 (Box 281, Folder 31)
  - Guggenheim, Mary, 1980 (Box 281, Folder 32)
  - H, 1975-1982 (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Hass, Robert B., 1980-1981 (Box 282, Folder 2)
  - Hagen, Laura, 1976 (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - Haggarty, Teddy M., 1975, 1981 (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - Hall, Donald, 1977-1978 (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Hallman, Frank, 1975 (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Hamady, Walter/ The Perishable Press Limited, 1975-1980 (Box 282, Folder 7)
  - Hanson, Nancy Kellog, 1979-1980 (Box 282, Folder 8)
  - Hargraves, Michael, 1979 (Box 282, Folder 9)
  - Harris, Mary Emma, 1980 (Box 282, Folder 10)
  - Hartman, Ray, 1980-1982 (Box 282, Folder 11)
  - Hanser, Susan, 1975-1976; 1978 (Box 282, Folder 12)
  - Healey, Clair, 1975; 1981-1982 (Box 282, Folder 13)
  - Heller, Michael, 1976; 1979-1982 (Box 282, Folder 14)
  - Hemesley, B., 1979-1981 (Box 282, Folder 15)
  - Hepworth, James R., 1975; 1976 (Box 282, Folder 16)
  - Herms, 1980-1982 (Box 282, Folder 17)
  - Higgins, Dick, 1975-1978 (Box 282, Folder 18)
  - Hindrichs, Werner S., 1982 (Box 282, Folder 19)
  - Hindus, Milton, 1976-1980 (Box 282, Folder 20)
  - Hirshhorn Museum, 1981 (Box 282, Folder 21)
  - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, 1975 (Box 282, Folder 22)
  - Hocks, Paula, 1982 (Box 282, Folder 23)
  - Horace Mann School, 1975 (Box 282, Folder 24)
  - I, 1977; 1979,; 1982, (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Ignatow, David, 1976, 1982 (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - Ingram Book Company, 1979 (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - International Bookfinders Inc. (Mohr, Richard), 1976, 1979-1981 (Box 283, Folder 4)
  - Intersection Poetry Series, 1977 (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - Irby, Ken, 1971 (Box 283, Folder 6)
  - J, 1976, 1979-1981 (Box 283, Folder 7)
  - Jacada Publications, 1977 (Box 283, Folder 8)
  - Jacobs, Yaakov, 1979-1980 (Box 283, Folder 9)
  - Jaffe, Sherril, 1976-1981 (Box 283, Folder 10)
  - Johnston, Alastair, 1975 (Box 283, Folder 11)
  - Jonas, Stephen (Rafael De Gruttola, Robert Kelly), 1974 (Box 283, Folder 12)
  - Jones, Bill, 1977-1978; 1981-1982 (Box 283, Folder 13)
  - Joris, Pierre, 1977; 1980 (Box 283, Folder 14)
  - K, 1977, 1980 (Box 284, Folder 1)
  - Keefe, Kathleen A., 1981 (Box 284, Folder 2)
  - Kelly, Robert (see also Jonas, Stephen), 1981 (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Kessler, Jascha, 1975; 1977,; 1981, (Box 284, Folder 4)
  - Kherdian, David, 1976 (Box 284, Folder 5)
  - Kitaj, R.B., 1980-1981 (Box 284, Folder 6)
  - Klauck, Daniel L., 1975-1978 (Box 284, Folder 7)
  - Klein, Philip C., 1976-1977 (Box 284, Folder 8)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1978 (Box 284, Folder 9)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard, 1975-1982 (Box 284, Folder 10)
  - Koller, James, 1976-1978 (Box 284, Folder 11)
  - L, 1975-1982 (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - L, 1975-1982 (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - Lally, Michael, 1978 (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - Lepper, Gary, 1976-1980 (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - Levin, Alexandra Lee, 1976-1977 (Box 285, Folder 5)
  - Levin, Lawrence L., 1976 (Box 285, Folder 6)
  - Levy, John, 1975-1978 (Box 285, Folder 7)
  - Library of Congress, Copyright Office, 1977-1978 (Box 285, Folder 8)
  - Litmus Inc. (Charles Potts), 1975-1976 (Box 285, Folder 9)
  - Little Press and Gallery, 1977; 1980, (Box 285, Folder 10)
  - Locklin, Gerry, 1976-1982 (Box 285, Folder 11)
  - Lodestone Books, 1977-1980 (Box 285, Folder 12)
  - Loewinsohn, Ron, 1976-1979 (Box 285, Folder 13)
  - London Magazine Editions, 1975 (Box 285, Folder 14)
  - M, 1975-1982 (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Macmillan Publishers, LTD., New Zealand, 1978 (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - Malanga, Gerard, 1974-1982 (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Maro Verlag, 1975; 1977,; 1982 (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Marder, Irving, 1980 (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Materer, Timothy, 1979-1981 (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - McBride Brothers and Broadley, LTD., 1979-1981 (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - McClure, Michael, 1977-1979; 1982 (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - McLaughlin, Thomas J., 1981-1982 (Box 286, Folder 9)
  - Mead, Gary, 1982 (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Meltzer, David, 1975; 1979-1981 (Box 286, Folder 11)
  - Menard Press (Anthony Rudolf), 1976-1978; 1980 (Box 286, Folder 12)
  - Meyers, Jeffrey, 1980; 1982, (Box 286, Folder 13)
  - Michel, Walter, 1980-1981 (Box 286, Folder 14)
  - Miller, Hugh, 1978 (Box 286, Folder 15)
  - Miller, Jeffrey, 1976-1982 (Box 286, Folder 16)
  - Montgomery, John, 1976-1980 (Box 286, Folder 17)
  - Moore, G. H., 1980 (Box 286, Folder 18)
  - Moos, Einar, 1979; 1982 (Box 286, Folder 19)
  - Morris, Wright, 1970 (Box 286, Folder 20)
  - Morrow, Bradford, 1970 (Box 286, Folder 21)
  - Moyo (Russell Esters), undated (Box 286, Folder 22)
  - Mudborn Press (Judyl Mudfoot, Sasha Newborn), 1977-1978 (Box 286, Folder 23)
  - Mudd, Harvey, 1981-1982 (Box 286, Folder 24)
  - Müller, Martin, 1981-1982 (Box 286, Folder 25)
  - Murray, Timothy D., 1979-1980 (Box 286, Folder 26)
  - N, 1975-1982 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - Naropa Institute, 1977-1979 (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - Navero, William, 1975-1976 (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - New Directions Publishing (James Laughlin), 1975; 1977,; 1979 (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - The Montemora Foundation, Inc. (Eliot Weinberger), 1976-1977 (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - New Letters, 1975; 1979 (Box 287, Folder 6)
  - Nicely, Tom, 1976 (Box 287, Folder 7)
  - No Mountains Poetry Project, 1975 (Box 287, Folder 8)
  - Noyes, Lucy Ferriss, 1974-1978 (Box 287, Folder 9)
  - O, 1977-1982 (Box 287, Folder 10)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol, 1975-1981 (Box 287, Folder 11)
  - Olson, Toby, 1975; 1977 (Box 287, Folder 12)
  - Oppen, George and Mary, 1977-1981 (Box 287, Folder 13)
  - Owens, Peter, LTD, 1975; 1977 (Box 287, Folder 14)
  - Owens, Rochelle, 1969; 1975-1980 (Box 287, Folder 15)
  - Oxford University Press, 1975; 1982 (Box 287, Folder 16)
  - P, 1975-1977; 1979-1982 (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Paideuma, 1978-1981 (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Palevsky, Joan, 1975-1976 (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Palmer, Michael, 1977-1980 (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Parmenter, Ross, 1975-1976; 1980 (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Peartree Books, 1975 (Box 288, Folder 6)
  - Pentagram Press, 1976-1977 (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Permissions (Pending), 1975-1980 (Box 288, Folder 8)
  - The Poetry Project, 1975 (Box 288, Folder 9)
  - Pociao’s Book Store, 1975-1976 (Box 288, Folder 10)
  - Pollini, Francis, 1978 (Box 288, Folder 11)
  - Postner, David, 1971 (Box 288, Folder 12)
  - Poulin, Al, 1975-1976 (Box 288, Folder 13)
  - Pound, Omar, 1980-1982 (Box 288, Folder 14)
  - Power, Kevin, 1977 (Box 288, Folder 15)
  - Prisons (by state); see also Klauck, Daniel L., 1975-1978; 1984 (Box 288, Folder 16)
  - Pushcart Press, 1975-1979 (Box 288, Folder 17)
  - Quality Paperback Book Service, Inc., 1975 (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Quasha, George, 1975-1976 (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - R, 1976-1982 (Box 289, Folder 3)
  - Rakosi, Carl, 1975-1982 (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - Rasula, Jed, circa 1975-1979 (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - Ravine, Edward, 1974-1975 (Box 289, Folder 6)
  - Rechy, John, 1976 (Box 289, Folder 7)
  - Reznikoff, Charles (Marie Syrkin, Camilla Reznikoff Wygan); See also: Hindus, Milton; Creeley, Robert; the Menard Press; California, University of San Diego—Library; Archive for New Poetry; United States Information Agency, 1975-1977 (Box 289, Folder 8)
  - Reznikoff, Charles, 1978-1982 (Box 289, Folder 9)
  - Richmond, Steve (Richmond: Book of Poems, Weissner, Carl: Letter 17/11/77), 1976-1978 (Box 289, Folder 10)
  - Rissman, John and Bob (Rissman, John: 4 Poems), 1977 (Box 289, Folder 11)
  - Roberts, F. Warren (David Farmer), 1975-1980 (Box 289, Folder 12)
  - Roberts, John, 1980-1981 (Box 289, Folder 13)
  - Roditi, Edouard, 1975-1983 (Box 289, Folder 14)
  - Rota, Bertram, LTD (Anthony Rota), 1976-1979 (Box 289, Folder 15)
  - Rothemberg, Jerome (Rothemberg: Abulafia’s Circles, 2 versions), 1975; 1978 (Box 289, Folder 16)
  - Rumaker, Michael (correspondence and poems), 1975-1978 (Box 289, Folder 17)
  - Rumaker, Michael (writings), 1965-1975 (Box 289, Folder 18)
  - S, 1975-1982 (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Sagar, Keith, 1976-1978 (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - The Poetry Center, San Francisco State University (newsletters, flyers), 1975-1979 (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - Sand Dollar, 1976 (Box 290, Folder 4)
  - Schuyler, James (Maxine Groffsky), 1978-1979 (Box 290, Folder 5)
  - Schwerner, Armano (writings), 1975 (Box 290, Folder 6)
  - Shakely, Lauren (poems), 1975-1976 (Box 290, Folder 7)
  - Shelmutt, Eve, 1979-1982 (Box 290, Folder 8)
  - Siegel, Bobbe, 1976 (Box 290, Folder 9)
  - Silbert, Layle, 1975-1982 (Box 290, Folder 10)
  - Simon and Schuster / Pocket Books, 1977 (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - Singh, G, 1975-1978 (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Skylo Book Distribution, 1977 (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - The Small Press Book Club, 1977 (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - Society of Author’s Representatives, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 291, Folder 5)
  - Spencer, Roy, 1975-1982 (Box 291, Folder 6)
  - Sorrentino, Gilbert, 1975-1982 (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - Stein, Gertrude (Maurice Grosser, writings), 1975 (Box 291, Folder 8)
  - Stephanchev, Stephen, 1975-1982 (Box 291, Folder 9)
  - Stephens, Christopher P. Booksellers, Inc., 1975 (Box 291, Folder 10)
  - Stevenson, Anne, 1977 (Box 291, Folder 11)
  - Steward, Lawrence P., 1976 (Box 291, Folder 12)
  - Stoher, Taylor, 1978-1980 (Box 291, Folder 13)
  - The Subterranean Company, 1977 (Box 291, Folder 14)
  - Swartz, S.C., 1978 (Box 291, Folder 15)
  - Syrkin, Marie (See also Reznikoff, Charles), 1978-1979 (Box 291, Folder 16)
  - T, circa 1972-1982 (Box 291, Folder 17)
  - Taggart, John, 1977 (Box 291, Folder 18)
  - Talon Books LTD (Box 291, Folder 19)
  - Tarn, Nathaniel, 1975-1982 (Box 291, Folder 20)
  - Thayler, Carl, 1975 (Box 291, Folder 21)
  - Thompson, William E. (Tom), 1977 (Box 291, Folder 22)
  - Truck Distribution Service (David Wilk), 1976-1977 (Box 291, Folder 23)
  - Two Hands Bookstore, 1977; 1980 (Box 291, Folder 24)
  - U, 1975 (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - Unicorn Press (Alan Brilliant, Paul Eluard - writings, 1976-1979 (Box 292, Folder 2)
  - United States Information Agency, 1978 (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - University of California Los Angeles Library, 1979-1981 (Box 292, Folder 4)
  - University of California San Diego Library, Archive for New Poetry Newsletter, 1975-1982 (Box 292, Folder 5)
  - University of California Santa Barbara Library, 1976; 1981 (Box 292, Folder 6)
  - V, 1977-1982 (Box 292, Folder 7)
  - Vanguard Press, Inc., 1975 (Box 292, Folder 8)
  - Vas Dias, Robert, 1978 (Box 292, Folder 9)
  - Verlag Buchse Der Pandora GMBH, 1978 (Box 292, Folder 10)
  - W, 1975-1981 (Box 292, Folder 11)
  - Wakoski, Diane, 1979-1981 (Box 292, Folder 12)
  - Waldman, Anne (writings), 1975-1977 (Box 292, Folder 13)
  - Weiss, Burton, 1977-1979 (Box 292, Folder 14)
  - Wellesley College Library, Special Collections (Eleanor L. Nicholes), 1976 (Box 292, Folder 15)
  - Wenning, Henry W., 1978 (Box 292, Folder 16)
  - White, Barbara A., 1978 (Box 292, Folder 17)
  - Whole Earth Center, 1975 (Box 292, Folder 18)
  - Wild and Wooley, 1977-1981 (Box 292, Folder 19)
  - Will, Frederic, 1978 (Box 292, Folder 20)
  - Williams, Gil and Deborah (The Bellevue Press), 1976; 1978 (Box 292, Folder 21)
  - Williams, Jonathan (writings), 1975-1981 (Box 292, Folder 22)
  - Wilson, Keith (writings), 1976 (Box 292, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Robert A., 1989 (Box 292, Folder 24)
  - Winans, Al, 1976 (Box 292, Folder 25)
  - Woolf, Douglas, 1975-1977 (Box 292, Folder 26)
  - Wright, F.N., 1978 (Box 292, Folder 27)
  - Y, circa 1975-1980 (Box 292, Folder 28)
  - Yellin, Herb, circa 1975-1980 (Box 292, Folder 29)
  - Young, William, 1979-1980 (Box 292, Folder 30)
  - Z, 1978-1981 (Box 292, Folder 31)
  - Zavatsky, Bill, 1976-1978 (Box 292, Folder 32)
  - Zytaruk, George J., 1976-1977 (Box 292, Folder 33)
- Series III: Publicity Materials, Publication Lists, 1966-1994
  This series publicity materials, new title catalogs, checklists, and order forms.
  - Black Sparrow Publicity Materials (Publicity, Press Releases), 1966-1994 (Box 293)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1957 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Flyers/Announcements, #24-26, 30, 35-36, 50-52, 54, 67-68, 69-70 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Flyers/Announcements, #71-71, 75-76, 79-81, 83-88, 90, 92-95, 97-99 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Flyers/Announcements, #101-102, 104-112, 114-116, 123- 129-130, 132, 136-137, 140, 144, 154, 156, 159 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1987-1990 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Book Reviews/Press Releases, 1986-1988 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Book Reviews/Press Releases, 1986-1988 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Book Reviews/Press Releases, 1991-1994 (Box 293, Folder 7)
  - Checklists and Order Forms, New Title Catalogs, 1966-1994 (Box 294)
    - Checklist and Order Form, undated (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - September 1968 – December 1974 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Fall/Winter 1975 (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Summer 1976 – Winter 1976/1977 (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - Summer/Fall/Winter 1977 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Spring/Summer 1978 (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - Fall/Winter 1978 (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Fall/Winter 1979 – Spring 1980 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Fall/Winter 1980 (Box 294, Folder 9)
    - Spring/Summer 1981 (Box 294, Folder 10)
    - Fall/Winter 1981 (Box 294, Folder 11)
    - Spring/Summer 1982 (Box 294, Folder 12)
    - Fall/Winter 1982 (Box 294, Folder 13)
    - Spring/Summer 1983 (Box 294, Folder 14)
    - Fall/Winter 1983 (Box 294, Folder 15)
    - Wyndham Lewis Brochure, 1983 (Box 294, Folder 16)
    - Spring/Summer, 1984 (Box 294, Folder 17)
    - Fall/Winter 1984 (Box 294, Folder 18)
    - Spring/Summer 1985 (Box 294, Folder 19)
    - Fall/Winter 1985 (Box 294, Folder 20)
    - Spring/Summer 1986 (Box 294, Folder 21)
    - Fall/Winter 1986 (Box 294, Folder 22)
    - Spring/Summer 1987 (Box 294, Folder 23)
    - Fall/Winter 1987 (Box 294, Folder 24)
    - Fall/Winter 1988 (Box 294, Folder 25)
    - Spring/Summer 1989 (Box 294, Folder 26)
    - Fall 1989 (Box 294, Folder 27)
    - Spring/Summer 1990 (Box 294, Folder 28)
    - Fall/Winter 1993 (Box 294, Folder 29)
- Series IV: Arabesque Books Collaborations, 1981
  This series includes titles published under the imprint Arabesque Books, and that was meant to focus on art books and portfolios. Harvey Mudd’s The Plain of Smokes includes original prints by Ken Price and Singular Aesthetic, by American photographer Paul Outerbridge, is a catalogue raisonne, or comprehensive listing of all his known works. Oversized items are located at the end of this series.
  - Mudd, Harvey, The Plain of Smokes, 1981 (Arabesque Books) (Box 295)
    - Correspondence (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - Artwork (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Discarded Materials (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Ken Price Articles (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - A Note on the Printing; A Note on the Text (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - 2 Original Serigraph Prints by Ken Price (File Copy and 19/26) – See Oversized Items, Box 298 (Box 295, Folder 7)
  - Outerbridge, Paul, Singular Aesthetic, 1981 (Arabesque Books) (Box 296)
    - Correspondence (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Discarded Materials (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - Flyers and Proofs (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - Half-title, Blank, Title Page, Verse Title Page (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Dedication, Epigraph, Acknowledgements, Table of Contents, Editor’s Introductions (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - Half-title, Footnotes, Figures and Captions (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - Platinum and Silver Bromide Prints: Half-title, Verso of Half-title, Title and Credit Index (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - Drawings: Half-title, Verso of Half-title, Title and Credit Index (Box 296, Folder 8)
    - Carbro-Color Prints, Half-title, Verso of Half-title, title and Credit Index (Box 296, Folder 9)
    - Supplementary Photographs, 1921-1941 (Box 296, Folder 10)
    - Appendix A: The Carbro Process; Appendix B: Editor’s Notes (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Appendix C: Chronology of Outerbridge’s Life; Appendix D: Selected Bibliography (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Appendix E: Institutional Collections; Appendix F: Exhibitions and Colophon (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - Layout Materials (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - Mock up (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Items, 1981-1990 (Box 298)
  - Mudd, Harvey, The Plain of Smokes. 2 Original Serigraph Prints by Ken Price, 1981 (File Copy and 19/26). #449 Hollywood, Bukowski, Charles, Cover Art Slides, 1989 (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - #462 Comics, Crumb, Robert. Artwork, 1990 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - #462 Comics, Crumb Robert. 1 Hardcover Copy, 1990 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - #463 Septuagenarian Stew, Bukoskwi, Charles, Artwork, 1990 (Box 298, Folder 4)
  - Clucas, Lowell, Winter Passage. Original (Poem on green paper). (Copy#7) (Box 298, Folder 5)